https://abortionclinics.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
COVID-19 Update: Our clinics are OPEN!
Donate
Select LanguageArabicChinese (Simplified)DutchEnglishFrenchGermanItalianPortugueseRussianSpanish
Abortions
Medication Abortion (Pill Abortions)
Abortions
Medication Abortion (Pill Abortions)
Bethesda, Maryland
Bellevue, Nebraska(402) 291-4797Bethesda, Maryland(301) 517-6810
Abortions
Medication Abortion (Pill Abortions)
Vasectomies
Select LanguageArabicChinese (Simplified)DutchEnglishFrenchGermanItalianPortugueseRussianSpanish
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Agreement was last modified on October 8th, 2016.
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
We're Here To Help!
Just select your location and use the simple form to schedule
Services provided in Bellevue, NE or Bethesda, MD
Schedule Now
SELECT A LOCATION
Bellevue, NE
Bethesda, MD
CARE
Clinics for Abortion & Reproductive Excellence
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
NEBRASKA LOCATION(402) 291-47971002 West Mission AvenueBellevue, Nebraska 680053
MARYLAND LOCATION(301) 517-681010401 Old Georgetown Road, Suite 104Bethesda, Maryland 20814
NEWS INQUIRESmichael@carerepro.org
Resources
Home
Donate
Pregnancy Calculator
Risk & Complications
About Us
Site Map
CONNECT
CARE provides Late Term Abortion, Third Trimester Abortion, Abortion After 27 Weeks, Maternal Indication Abortion, Fetal Indication Abortion, Birth Control, STD Testing and Treatment services our clinics are located in
Bellevue, Nebraska and
Bethesda, Maryland. CARE services
Alabama,
Alaska,
Arizona,
Arkansas,
California,
Colorado,
Connecticut,
Delaware,
Florida,
Georgia,
Hawaii,
Idaho,
Illinois,
Indiana,
Iowa,
Kansas,
Kentucky,
Louisiana,
Maine,
Maryland,
Massachusetts,
Michigan,
Minnesota,
Mississippi,
Missouri,
Montana,
Nebraska,
Nevada,
New Hampshire,
New Jersey,
New Mexico,
New York,
North Carolina,
North Dakota,
Ohio,
Oklahoma,
Oregon,
Pennsylvania,
Rhode Island,
South Carolina,
South Dakota,
Tennessee,
Texas,
Utah,
Vermont,
Virginia,
Washington,
West Virginia,
Wisconsin,
Wyoming,
as well as surrounding areas.
